[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Pulp Fiction, Butch (Bruce Willis character) asks English Dave, the bartender at Sally Leroys, for a pack of cigarettes of what brand?", "correct_answer": "Red Apple", "incorrect_answers": ["Marlboro", "Lucky Strike", "Camel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award did the 1997 comedy movie Men in Black receive?", "correct_answer": "Best Makeup", "incorrect_answers": ["Best Art Direction", "All of these", "Best Original Score"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Back to the Future, Doc Brown asked Marty to meet him at the mall at what time?", "correct_answer": "1:15 am", "incorrect_answers": ["High Noon", "2:15 am", "Midnight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor won his first Academy Award for Best Actor for portraying painter and writer Christy Brown in the 1989 movie My Left Foot.", "correct_answer": "Daniel Day-Lewis", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Lemmon", "Gene Hackman", "Kevin Spacey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do you say apple in Spanish?", "correct_answer": "manzana", "incorrect_answers": ["apio", "arroz", "uva"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the obese German boy reply to his mother when she tells him to stop eating himself in the 2005 movie Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?", "correct_answer": "But I taste so good!", "incorrect_answers": ["I cant hear you, I have chocolate in my ears!", "But Im starving!", "Nobody can tell me what to do!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the only American President to be elected to office in the Confederacy ?", "correct_answer": "John Tyler", "incorrect_answers": ["Zachary Taylor", "Andrew Jackson", "Millard Fillmore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Personalities of this sign are either leaders or rebels.  Unless in a position of authority, males of this sign are outspoken critics of those above them.", "correct_answer": "Tiger", "incorrect_answers": ["Dragon", "Snake", "Dog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these languages does not belong to the Germanic language family?", "correct_answer": "Finnish", "incorrect_answers": ["Icelandic", "Swedish", "Norwegian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "U2s song Sweetest Thing was reportedly written by vocalist Bono as an apology to his wife Ali Hewson for forgetting this.", "correct_answer": "Forgetting her birthday", "incorrect_answers": ["Forgetting their wedding anniversary", "Forgetting to feed her cat", "Forgetting to pick her mother from the airport"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not one of Godzillas varied abilities?", "correct_answer": "Laser vision", "incorrect_answers": ["Tremendous strength", "Atomic breath", "Breathing underwater"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In What About Bob?, when Dr. Marvin finally gets home, the family treats him to a surprise birthday party. What does Dr. Marvin see that pushes him over the edge?", "correct_answer": "Bob with his arm around Dr. Marvins sister, Lily", "incorrect_answers": ["Bob carrying the cake and licking the frosting", "Bob with his arms around Dr. Marvins kids", "Bob opening one of Dr. Marvins presents"]}]